> > 布莱恩: 另一个很酷的事情是你可以建立一个设计系统
&gt;&gt; Brian: Another cool thing here is that
you can kind of build design systems
变成这样
into this.
所以我想让你做个新文件
So I want you to make a new file and
在源目录中此处调用 colors.css 。
call it colors.css here
in the source directory.
或者对不起 colors.js，相反
Or sorry, colors.js, rather.
>> Brian: 我希望您在此处仅导出缺省对象。
&gt;&gt; Brian: And I want you to make
just export default object here.
你可以在这里用一些颜色或者类似的颜色，对吧。
And just, you can put in like some colors
here or something like that, right.
因此，我可以说主导出缺省值。
So I could say primary export default.
> > 布莱恩: 我们会说，我有什么， bf3334。
&gt;&gt; Brian: And we'll say like,
what do I have, bf3334.
辅助服务器为 #d9c148。
Secondary is #d9c148.
> > 布莱恩: 黑暗是 122622#
&gt;&gt; Brian: Dark is 122622#.
>> Brian: 光明。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Light is.
>> Brian: #81a69b。
&gt;&gt; Brian: #81a69b.
所以现在我在一个地方都有这些颜色，对吧 ?
So now I have all these
colors in one place, right?
所以我可以去我的酒吧
So, I can actually come
over to my nav bar.
> > 布莱恩: 你不用完全复制我的颜色。
&gt;&gt; Brian: You don't have
to copy my colors exactly.
如果你想的话你可以把粉色放进去
You could put pink in
there if you want to.
> > 布莱恩: 关键是你可以在这里看到，
&gt;&gt; Brian: The point is
that you can see here,
您可以集中所有设计系统，样式指南或
you could centralize all of your
design system, your style guide, or
不管你想说什么这里就有一个地方
whatever you wanna call it,
here in one place.
现在我可以将它导入到我的代码中。
And now I can import this into my code.
我可以用点颜色说进口颜色对吧
I can say import colors from .colors,
right?
这不是粉红色的背景我可以的
Instead of having pink as
the background here, I can have it be.
>> Brian: colors.primary，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: colors.primary, right?
所以现在如果我到这里，那将会是一个很不错的红色的树荫。
So now if I go over here,
it would be a nice shade of red.
或者我可以放色彩色的
Or I can put colors.secondary.
>> 布莱恩: 对，现在的东西越来越多了，
&gt;&gt; Brian: Right, and
now stuff is starting to match more,
因为那是这个网站的实际颜色。
because those are the actual
colors of the site.
我还是觉得粉色不错，你问我也行。
I still think the pink was nice,
if you ask me, but this is fine too.
所以，让我们说，我们想在狮子狗上拥有某种悬浮状态。
So, let's say we wanted to have some
sort of hover state on the poodle.
这在这里很容易做到，你只需将鼠标悬停在其中。
That's pretty easy to do here,
you just put &amp;:hover.
这感觉很熟悉你以前就像个混蛋一样
This feels pretty familiar if you've done
like sass before or something like that.
然后是文本装饰: 下划线。
And then text-decoration: underline.
所以我们就加了这个
So we just added that.
现在，如果你回来的话
And now, if you come back over here.
我怎么弄坏的
How did I break it?
太棒了
That's impressive.
不知道我这里是否有个奇怪的状态
I wonder if I got into
a strange state here.
> > 布莱恩: 我觉得我的包裹刚刚坏了。
&gt;&gt; Brian: I think my parcel just broke.
好了这样你就可以把它悬停在狗上并强调它
Okay, so that's works now so
you can hover on the dog and underline it.
这就是你喜欢悬浮状态和敌人的方式
That's how you do like hover states and
befores and afters and
都是那种东西
all that kind of stuff.
你也可以在下面做儿童选择器，如果你需要的话，对吧 ?
You can also do child selectors underneath
that as well if you needed to, right?
所以如果我有一个孩子的按钮你就可以
So if I had like a child button,
you could just put,
我想你只要按按钮就好了
I think you just put button and
I think it would just work.
立即的儿童选择器，所有这些东西。
And immediate child selector,
all that kind of stuff.
您可以使用和作为实际组件本身的替身。
You can use and as a stand-in for
the actual component itself.
> > 布莱恩: 好吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay?